Moisés Navarro Galván

Java Software Developer

About me

I am a dedicated and solution-focused Software Engineer with over Seven years of expertise in Java and Spring, bolstered by five years' experience in the fast-paced and demanding banking industry. With a rich history working in Scrum and Waterfall methodologies.

I am constantly striving to learn and implement new technologies, aiming to maximize development efficiency and product quality.

Experience

Software Consultant at Deloitte

January 2024 - Current

Bugfix and Development of new components for Google Cloud Platform

Software Developer at IBM

March, 2022 - January 2024

Bugfix and development of new software components for The Home Depot US

Bugfix for the Dinner's Club bank of Ecuador

Software Engineer at Diebold Nixdorf

February, 2021 - March, 2022

Resolution of bugs and migration of software components for the upgrade project of Banco HSBC de México

Software Developer at Tata Consultancy Services

May, 2017 - February, 2021

Migration of applications and development of new software components for Banco Santander de México

Education

Engineering Degree, Universidad Tecnológica de Querétaro Software development and management

Sep, 2022 - Sep, 2024

Associate Degree, Universidad Tecnológica de Querétaro Information and communication technologies

Sep, 2015 - Ago, 2017

Contact

Santiago de Querétaro, México moises.navarro1408@gmail.com (+52)4424003122

Social Networks

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Skills

Java Spring Boot Scrum React MySql

Oracle SQL Linux

Linux Git

Maven SonarQube Websphere

GCP

Languages

Spanish (Native)
English (B2 Upper Intermediate)